okay first and foremost let me just say congratulations to my girl quinta brunson
for always being fabulous skilled comedic genius etc however this is not something to celebrate
quinta brunson is the first black comedy lead actress winner in more than 40 years at the
okay so as funny as we sisters are you know what maybe i need to remind y'all what y'all know about
nail carter of course claire huxtable dark skin out viv yes nisi damn gina dwine frederica brooks
real ones know tachina loves chris okay watermelandria and that's just to name a few how'd
she get in there let me just make it clear in 2024 anytime a headline says first black that ain't
something that we should be cheering that is something that everybody should be like damn
that's embarrassing about except for the first black because they like it's about damn motherfucking
time hey quinta